

DREW WOLFSON

WEB DEVELOPER DESIGNER

516-662-8519 | drewwolfson1@gmail.com









CLICK ME!

ABOUT ME

Hello World! I'm Drew, I'm certified in both design and programming, I'm a world traveler, creative enthusiast, innovator, concert junkie and film lover. I harness both passion and experience across full spectrum content creation to developmental



EDUCATION

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT
GENERAL ASSEMBLY | NOV 2015 - FEB 2016
HTML. CSS & WEB DESIGN CIRCUITS

BACHELOR'S DEGREE WEST VIRGINIA UNIVERSITY | 2009 - 2012 MAJOR'S IN ENGLISH, PUBLIC RELATIONS & COMMUNICATION STUDIES



SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Java Script
- React
- AJAX

- jQuery
- Handlebars
- API's
- WordPress
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Ruby on Rails
- Node.js
- Express
- MongoDB
- SQL



EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER | MAY 2016-PRESENT

- Develop concepts and maintain optimal workflow
- Collaborate with clients to create an intuitive interaction
- Prioritize and manage multiple projects
- Wireframe design and blue prints reflecting client needs

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER GENERAL ASSEMBLY | NOV 2016-MAY 2016

- Designed, developed and deployed full-stack web apps
- Managed full software development lifecycle
- Bridged gaps between user needs and graphical UI
- Operated numerous frameworks and program languages

HEAD OF DEVELOPMENT

TROY CURTIS ENTERTAINMENT | AUG 2014-NOV 2015

- Head of strategic development and branding efforts
- Designed all branding concepts and adverts
- Oversaw all digital media services

DIGITAL MARKETING & BUSINESS

DEVELOPMENT COORDINATOR

ERNST & YOUNG | DEC 2013 - SEPT 2014

- Coordinated national business developmental initiatives
- Operated advanced analytics to cross reference logistics
- Developed regional email templates
- Implemented numerous cross-media elements

SALES & MARKETING MANAGER
EIGHT TO EIGHTY EYEWEAR | AUG 2012-DEC 2013

- B2B/Outbound marketing and sales approaches
- Generated coast efficient team leads
- Managed email subscribers and weekly blasts
- Designed developmental marketing strategies



HOBBIES

- Design
- Coding
- Horror Movies
- Spotify
- Software
- Photography
- Comics
- Biking

- Tech News
- Code Academy
- UFC
- Eating Lobster
- Netflix weekends
- Reading comics
- Videogames
- Creative Approaches